"Minister Kim's Dream Life"
Fortunately, I keep exercising
Come on
(The top of Wolryong Mountain)
(Yuelong Mountain)
(Beware of wildfires)
I’m so exhausted
Hello, I am Kim Nak-soo, the manager of the ACT sales team.
I read your diary, senior
can you help me
Even if you just give me a little advice
I will be forever grateful
please help me
Senior?
Sunday 11am
See you at the top of Wolryong Mountain
What?
Senior?
Meet at Wollong Mountain at 11 o'clock?
Abominable
Why can't we say it on the phone?
Why do you have to let me climb up?
(Beware of wildfires)
Volcanic heart is small
"Small volcanic heart"?
- Small volcano heart
-"Beware of wildfires"?
you are late
Sorry, I'm too tired to climb this mountain.
- Burning is prohibited
- thank you
Ban on burning
-"Burning ban"?
- Burning is prohibited
-"Burn the ban..."
(burning is prohibited)
"No burning" I will keep it in mind
God, you've really aged a lot.
Sorry, do you know me?
Job interview
- Job interviews
-"Job interview"?
-"Interview interview"
"Job interview"
Entry interview!
Then go see the client first instead of going to the hospital
(Interviewer)
He's really crazy. He's insane.
You are the one who recruited me into ACT
Oops
Oh my god
How did you mess up so badly?
Maybe it's because I'm not good enough
Of course it is, no need to explain in detail
Yes
- Small volcano heart
-"Small volcano heart"
- Environmental protection
- "Environmental environment..."
Do you have one or two hundred million won?
- What?
- Yes or no?
Why ask this?
What why?
So I can help you
Put money in your boss's mouth!
I'll be the middleman to make sure nothing goes wrong
- What?
- I only need 5%
Senior, please forgive me.
Did you use this method to return to the headquarters back then?
No, of course not!
Then why did you let me...
Because you don’t have the wisdom like me
No
What is the position of leader of the safety management team?
Although it looks like a useless decoration
But the headquarters wants to assign various secret tasks
This location couldn't be better.
Really? But I haven't received any tasks.
You will know soon
you came just in time
Sorry what do you mean?
It’s been more than ten years since I retired
"ten years"
But I can still hear rumors about the company now
Please tell me straight
The headquarters assigns you a task
Be sure to finish it cleanly
That will be your chance of survival
You can use this
good
I'm hungry!
- Small volcano heart
- Environmental protection
Volcanic heart is small
Hey! Keep your back straight
Let’s transfer Kim Nak-soo back to the headquarters, senior.
What are you talking about?
I said if you want to bring Jin Luozhu back, just bring him back.
What do you mean?
Now that things have happened, I suddenly say this
Not so sudden
When Heo Tae-hwan resigned
Someone has to fill that gap.
Stop talking nonsense
Why did you mention this?
So worried
Huh?
It's because of Asan
What happened to the factory?
It's a long story
But the human resources team
The biggest battlefield this year is the Asan factory
So we need Kim Nak-su sunbaenim’s help
Are you sure?
(Executive Director)
(Minister Kim Nak-soo)
Episode 6: A glimmer of hope
The headquarters assigns you a task
Be sure to finish it cleanly
That will be your chance of survival
It's been several days and nothing has happened.
Does he know what he's talking about?
come here
You haven't had a security check in four days.
(check result)
Is this how you cope?
Even if I check it, I still can’t understand it.
and
It wasn't you who asked me to be quiet
And then leave?
Are you a child?
In this factory where you can’t have lunch if you run too slowly
Can't I still be like a child?
Of course
What if there was an accident on the day I drew the circle?
As long as you act like an adult
Just take responsibility
Instead of worrying about an accident
It’s better to take safety precautions seriously
Improve flexibility and reduce risk of injury, right?
I also want to do well
But the one in front of me
It's too stiff
Oh my god
Chengjiu!
hey
Minister!
I have to meet with the production team
Okay, contact me later
Okay I'm going to be late
OK go ahead
He was my subordinate at headquarters
I told him to just send him an email.
But he had to come all the way to report to me face to face
Oh my, this kid really can't adapt.
Oops
Where has she gone?
I wonder if he has eaten?
Don't worry. I'll take care of it, okay? It's okay...
she's coming
you stay here
This car is great. It drives so smoothly.
Brother-in-law, this car is great!
Oh yes
"Of course, I know you will never fail the exam."
Stop talking
Did you pass the pet undertaker exam?
I heard that this exam is particularly difficult
- Give me an iced coffee.
- thank you
I'm leaving
Wait, sister
This time it was Ha Young who was a little reckless.
She has been reckless all her life
So could you please let her go just this once...
Please think again
Sister, I'm sorry
What should I do, Ha Young?
Forget it
Stop nagging and take it.
- Okay
- OK
-Thank you for the car
- Take it
Wife, please, sister!
Just this once, please
please
- Hey!
-Sister
What are you doing?
- Sorry
- What?
Say it again louder
- Sorry
- Right, that's it
I won't look down on you again, I promise
Give me the car back
- Okay, I understand. I'm leaving.
- OK
Wait, sister!
- I'm really sorry
- Hey!
- Sister, I'm so sorry.
Please, sister, can you let me go this time?
I'm really sorry
What on earth was I thinking?
- Sister, please let me go this time. Please?
- Hey
enough
Watching a performance worth 90 million won is enough
Hey, what can I do with your car?
awesome
Can I borrow it for a day?
OK, of course
I'm so sorry, sister
Oh my, I love you so much
Me too! I love you so much!
- What?
- I mean...
Sorry. Thank you so much.
And Park Ha-jin
- Real estate agent!
- Congratulations!
- I'm leaving
- OK
Well done
Sorry, one more thing
I have to do it
Otherwise, my heart will be knotted
Can't solve it
Do you understand?
come on
Wait...
Yes! This is what a new car should be like
So cool
Chinstrap
Does this need some oil?
What?
- Minister Kim!
- Chengjiu Hey
- I have to meet with the logistics team.
- Really?
Logistics group...
Oops, this is dangerous
- What?
-Does this need to be tidied up?
- Okay. See you later.
- OK
contact me
Clean it up quickly.
Such dangerous things can't stay here
(Security Management Group)
Why haven't you come yet?
(Zheng Chengjiu)
"When will you arrive?"
Forget it, wait.
What is this?
Minister Kim!
Oops, this place is so hard to find. Sorry I'm late.
It's okay It's okay
Is everything done?
Yes
Good
Take a seat
You must be very busy. I didn't bother you, right?
No, it's okay. I've almost finished everything today.
OK!
I'm not with you, you haven't even drank this well, right?
Ouch
- Okay, drink it.
- Oops
I should have come to see you a long time ago. I'm so sorry.
It's okay. You must be very busy. How is the company doing?
Well... Section Chief Song, Song Xi and me
For the time being, we will follow the instructions of the capital minister.
We are all still adapting.
As the saying goes, you don’t know that spring has come until the flowers fall.
We all said: "When Minister Kim was here
Life is much better”
sorry
I should have always protected you
That's right. When will you come back, Minister?
How do I know?
I...
Oh, monitor Li
Agent Zheng, please say hello.
This is Li Zhuying, the monitor of our factory
She is our trump card
hello nice to meet you
I am agent Zheng Chengjiu from the sales team at the headquarters
Do you have something to report?
Dog food bowls are attracting flies
The poop bag is also full. Please take it out and throw it away.
I washed the water bowl
Anyway
You continue to work with Mr. Bai
Wouldn't it be better to stay in touch?
You're on the sales team anyway.
There's no one else to rely on
At this time, you need to show your loyalty more
Otherwise, how could there be a turnaround?
Oops, where is my laptop?
Here it is
(The Power of Jealousy Kim Soo-gyeom)
"Kim Soo Kyum"?
(Loan repayment notice)
"Loan"?
(Repayment details as of July 2025)
(Total loan amount: 30 million won)
I like it so much
This culture of drinking during the day is great.
Not that serious
Kim Soo Kyum?
Do you all know about this?
(Loan repayment notice)
Is this number empty?
try again
I've called it a dozen times
Hey, he's in Los Angeles now
- What?
Wait, this bastard took out a loan in our name.
And then ran away?
Can't believe it
I guess he even took away all the investment money.
What a complete scumbag!
Wait a minute
How much money did he loan in our name?
30 million won per person
- Thirty million?
Thirty million
- I was planning to buy a new car
- Hey
Let's get the money
The above account will suffice, right?
I promised my girlfriend that I would go to Ibiza
The money was returned
me too
- I'm going to be extremely poor these days.
- Yeah
Wait
Have you all paid back the money?
Yes, I feel so awkward
This matter must be resolved immediately
What to do now?
What else can we do? Take this opportunity to go back
- We have to get ready to go back to school.
- Yeah, Korea is quite interesting.
Quite fun
Goodbye, never see you again
Goodbye
take care
Aren't you leaving?
Damn this bastard
At least pay the electricity bill before running away?
Lee Jung Hwan, you bastard!
(Specialist Shen Kangxun)
- The number you dialed...
- Damn it, shut down again
he doesn't tell me anything
How should I prepare?
Damn, what a complete liar.
He wolfed down the medicinal duck soup
I should have known this after eating five large scallion pancakes
I still believe him. What an idiot.
Damn it
Alas
(Staff dormitory)
Who is it?
What are you doing here?
Wife!
I didn't even make a call. Why are you here?
It's dangerous so late
Let me give you a surprise
You really surprised me
Where did you get this car?
I...
Won the prize
Please stop joking
Seriously, where did you get the car?
Really, I'll go in and talk to you slowly.
- Wait, I'm going to take out the trash first.
- OK
Really? The car belongs to Ha Young?
Of course
Her brother-in-law bought her a new car
Don't crash other people's cars. Drive carefully.
Come
Come in!
Ouch, what are these? It’s so heavy.
OK come on
Take a look...
- You haven't had dinner yet?
- Nope
I'll cook hot pot for you
OK
put on top
- In here?
- Right put the freezer layer
good
Is Sang Cheol's company open?
Opened long ago
We also hired people and held an opening ceremony.
That's it
Why do you ask?
Nothing. Do you need my help?
Oops, the sun is coming out in the west?
Please, let me help
We can get it done quickly. What do you want me to do?
You have been doing housework for several months. Do you understand?
We really need to calculate housework on an hourly basis
That's no joke
Yes you are right
good
- Wife
- Oh, you scared me.
I almost cut my hand
Wife
Why are you doing this? Stop making trouble
- Will you stay tonight?
- No, I have to go home.
- Don't leave
- Don't do this
- Stop it
- Are you crazy?
- Have another baby?
Have another baby?
- I want a daughter
- Oops
- I really want a daughter
- Stop it
Soo Gyeom is no longer cute
- They don't even listen to me.
- Oh my God!
- Seriously, stop it!
- What?
Really
Oops
- Let's eat
You can tell by looking at it that it will be delicious.
- Awesome
- Look!
- wow
- OK
have a drink
thank you
I want it too
Pour you some
- Come
- Cheers
Cheers
(The monthly salary will be cut off and the monthly rent will not be)
What is that?
What?
that flyer
Don't know
You glued it together with tape and you still say you don’t know?
I don't know. Why is this thing here?
I don't know
Ah, it’s been a long time since I had a home-cooked meal.
looks delicious
How long do you have to stay here?
Well, not everyone can do this position.
Waiting for a suitable replacement to be found
I will go back naturally
Then you can't go back to the headquarters
I told you, this is executive coaching.
You can't go back
I told you that's not the case
If you yell at me again, I will go home
Oops
Stop denying it and explain it to me.
I have to find out what's going on, right?
What are you going to do?
What to do?
Do you want to hold on or are you planning to resign?
Maybe I'll go back
ok
But what if I can’t go back?
Oh, it's true
Don't resign out of anger
I know it's a bit selfish to say that.
But please don't do that
We need to plan for the next few years
You also know about the loan
Soo-gyeom is just a freshman
Even if he has a family, he can handle it by himself
But we have to support him until he graduates.
Don't waver just for the severance pay. Just hold on.
I...
I can help now too
What does it mean?
I didn't mean to tell you this
What's wrong? Tell me
I passed the real estate agent exam
What?
I secretly prepared for the exam without letting you know. I passed the exam.
I really can't believe it
What did you take me for?
What else can I take you for?
I don't think of you as a superhero
Or "Hundred Battles with Heavenly Dragons"
I just think of you as the Kim Nak Soo I know
and then make a decision
I mean...
Do you think making money is as easy as it sounds?
Do you think I...
No, I just...
I really don't want to see you like this
Oops
You go
Did she really pass the real estate agent exam?
What if I get fired...
She is the only one working...
What a wise choice
Waiting for you to pay the deposit
- We will help you immediately...
- Oops
- ...Go through the signing procedures
- that's it
Hello!
What are you doing?
Turn off!
Yes
Your ID card...
Please don't do this. You make me uncomfortable.
- Sang Cheol!
- let me go
Sang Cheol!
Deposit, down payment and installment payment
Every transaction will not be stressful
Who is that guy?
We met at work. Leave me alone.
Did they really meet at work?
Really?
Oh my god
Don't go drinking with him
Clean the house!
Wife
Wife...
No!
This is not okay!
He just stopped for a while
Why did the commotion start again?
Leave him alone
Think about how uncomfortable he must be
Kim Nak Soo!
Who is he?
I'm a minister
I had a smooth journey
Never miss a promotion opportunity
thank you
I am a famous college student recruited through open recruitment
The best of the best
I will be promoted to a senior executive next year, 99.9% no problem
Do you know?
Dog food bowls are attracting flies
The poop bag is also full. Please take it out and throw it away.
I bought an apartment in Seoul
It's my own money!
I sent my son to college!
I worked in a big company
25 years
I'm still a minister!
You bastards!
Damn it!
Why do you do this to me?
What the hell is going on?
(Executive Director Bai Zhengtai)
Kim Nak Soo
Yes, Executive Bai
Why is it so noisy over there?
Can you hear me?
Yes can hear
You often scold me behind my back, right?
No, of course not
Stop pretending, kid
Have you eaten?
four, five, six, seven, eight
two, two, three, four
five, six, seven, eight
five
- How about this? Can you see it?
- visible
- Okay, let's shoot
- Yes
three
one, two, three
Oops
I have to go to the headquarters later
I didn't ask you
Not only do safety management but also reporting to the headquarters...
I'm so busy Oops
(reception desk payment desk)
(Five safety rules
Safety Operation Logistics Inspection)
(Safety Checklist Factory Safety Inspection)
(Benefits of safe exercise)
Hey hyung, it’s me Kim Nak-soo
Are we going to have dinner together tonight?
Yeah, I've sent you the address.
What's wrong? What happened?
No, I just called to confirm.
- Okay, see you then.
- Oh, one more thing.
Is this the logistics team or the production team?
Want me to prepare some training materials
I'll send it to you later
Can you give me some feedback?
I feel a little rusty lately
Not sure how prepared it is
I don't understand this at all
Does my opinion matter?
It's okay. Can you scan it quickly?
I'll send it to you shortly
ok ok
See you later. Thank you.
You can do it Kim Nak-soo
Does anyone have plans for tonight?
It's okay, just say it
we have no arrangements
We're fine too
How about having a dinner with the sales team tonight?
- OK! Team dinner!
- Awesome
OK
Would you like to book your favorite craft beer house?
It's really nice there, but Songxi
Is it Minister?
Go to the restaurant your group usually goes to. I want to try it.
Good
After I meet the client, I'll go over there and meet you.
Send me the address
- Good Minister
- See you at the restaurant
- Okay. See you later.
- See you soon, Minister.
- See you later
- Be careful on the road
What are you doing?
I have to sell this and pay back the interest first.
(Coffee machine for sale, please contact us)
Hey what is this?
Do you want to buy it when you see it?
What if? What should I do?
Are you selling this?
Yes
(Edit second-hand product post)
(Less than one year old, includes two packs of coffee beans)
How did you come up with these words so easily?
I'm just listing the facts.
The more useless details there are, the less credible it becomes.
Is there anything else for sale?
"Professional high-end audio"
turntables and bluetooth devices
"Medieval simplicity..."
"Medieval style"? What is it?
Medieval retro style
If you take it with the desk, I'll give you 300,000
- 250,000, right?
- 280,000
- 260,000
Okay 270,000!
275,000?
No more
Great. We made money!
(Oson Market)
You can also send it to a convenience store
I will wrap it up
Good
- Okay, let's go to the convenience store.
- let's go
thank you
- take care
- thank you
(The power of jealousy)
Ah I'm so hungry
Aren't you hungry?
I'm hungry too
Let's go
I want a bacon lettuce and tomato sandwich
Good
Let’s get started!
As the saying goes: “If you don’t work, don’t eat.”
It must mean that the food tastes better after work.
This bagel is so delicious
Do you want to order another one to share?
Let's have one more person
We made 3.8 million won today
- Yeah, please order more.
- Order it
We work well together, right?
Hannah, since the momentum is good
Why don't we buy some goods?
Seriously, start selling, right?
How much money can be spent to purchase goods?
I already owe 30 million won
I'm going to find investors
put on coat
Let's go
good
Hurry up
Very good
It's been a long time since we said goodbye. Have you always been in good health?
Kim Nak-soo, the incompetent villain, would like to say hello to you.
What are you doing? Come on in
This is a hangover cure, brother
Oh my god
There is also an interdental brush for use after meals.
thank you
Come
Oh thank you
- thank you
- Please use it slowly
OK thank you
Come and try the radish sprouts
Please enjoy
Do you want a treat?
thank you for your treat
- Let's get started
- OK
Brother
I learned a lot in the factory during this time
I feel like all my time in the company was wasted.
I didn’t communicate well with the team members either.
Actually, I really appreciate you sending me to the factory
If I hadn't gone to the factory
I may never understand in my life
thank you
- Then I'll feel relieved
- Yeah
Wait, I'll pour it
Come
- I'll pour you a drink
- OK
thank you
It's been a long time since I've been like this...
Oops
- Team leader!
- Here!
thank you
Said it was a dinner party tonight
But I’m not asking everyone to come back until they get drunk.
We'll just eat for an hour and then go home.
- OK
- Yes
Let's get started
- Please enjoy
- Enjoy
Please enjoy, team leader
It’s really like a team dinner in an old Korean drama
Really?
After all, Minister Kim Nak-soo is an old-school person.
This style suits him very well
Well, he is much older than the capital minister...
Hey, finished drinking
Where is the wine?
I'll get it
I've had Xinqi soup here several times at noon
But the taste is different at night
Yes
The soup base they use for lunch and evening is different
Use rice water at noon and replace it with broth at night
The boss said the soup for lunch was too greasy.
It is easy to have indigestion when working in the afternoon
So, the soup base changes back and forth.
Wow, Minister, you are so awesome.
The same goes for you, Agent Zheng
What?
I mean you're flexible.
Both you and your boss are flexible.
Yeah, I'm quite flexible.
bottle opener
- Bottle opener?
- Right
Didn't you bring it with you?
- sorry
- It's okay. I'll get it.
Are you going? Just inside
By the way, is the minister okay?
Which minister are you talking about?
Minister Kim Nak-soo
Didn’t you go to the Asan Factory a while ago?
Yes
I lost the guessing game and had to go!
You must have lost on purpose. You value friendship so much.
No, it's not like that, Minister.
Is that why he called us here?
That's right
And I'm on a business trip, so I have to run around.
I didn’t even have time to smoke a cigarette with Minister Kim.
But you still have to take good care of him
I might have to work under him someday.
It's unlikely that this will happen.
Who knows? Things are unpredictable.
If senior comes back
I will definitely welcome you with both hands
I still have a lot to learn
Come on, pour the wine and let's have a drink.
OK
- Everybody pour the wine
- OK
I'll do it, team leader
How can we have such excellent team members?
I'm such a lucky team leader
Come to the sales team!
- Come on!
- Come on
Oops
What else?
Oops, I'm so full. I can't eat anymore.
If you have your favorite shrimp, I’m sure you can have some more
Brother, did you read what I sent you?
Yeah
I watched
That's what I got out of temporarily
What do you think?
Not bad
Since you were a newcomer
The documentation is beautifully done
Where where...
I'm not here to hear praise
If there is anything that needs improvement, please give me some advice.
Are you serious?
Of course
What did you want to tell me when you made that report?
What?
That report was written specifically for me to read.
Isn't it?
I told you
That's for internal factory training.
It’s about the positive impact of stability on productivity...
Okay. Then what?
What do you suggest we do?
Creating a more equal organizational culture...
Create an equal organizational culture
Is that your duty at the factory?
To be honest, I really don't understand
What did you want to do with that report?
Or want to express something
no clue
Although the report is neat and beautiful
but no substance
Well...
I still have a lot to learn, bro.
I'll remember it. Sorry.
Luo Zhu
Huh?
I think that report
It explains your problem very well.
you guy
you are not working
if i wasn't at work
So what am I doing?
You're pretending to be working
Work is about responsibility
But you took no responsibility
No, you don't even know how to take responsibility
I was transferred to the factory
Are you saying you won't take responsibility?
You really haven't changed at all
You were indeed a good team member before
But after all
Failure to be a good leader
- Luo Su
- Wait a minute, bro.
You asked me to come all the way today
Just to say this?
I said it out of concern for you.
I'm worried about you
Is it because you care about me and worry about me?
Okay, anyway, I came to you today because...
No
Do you have the right to worry about me?
What?
It was you who pushed me into the pit of fire
I mean, how could the perpetrator worry about the victim?
Kim Nak Soo, you are really...
I'm not working?
So what have I been doing for the past 25 years?
You really don't understand, right?
Yes, I don’t understand
So I'm over 50 years old and I'm still shoveling dog poop in the factory.
You're perfect for that job, brat.
Am I pretending to be at work?
So what does it mean to wash your underwear and socks?
It's not even work, right?
What are you talking about?
If we let the team members do this kind of thing now,
Just wait for the lawsuit
When did I ask you to wash your underwear?
Then go sue me!
You've never worked with young people, but I have
I'm between you and them
Please please both sides
That’s why I brought you to where you are today!
What do you say to me now?
What about you?
Who do you think helped you keep your job?
Are you saying it's all thanks to you?
Of course it's me, idiot!
You should have been fired!
I risked my life to save you!
That’s why you were just transferred to Asan! Do you understand?
You boy
I don't know
I really don't know at all
I thought it was because Du Zhenyu was more useful than me.
I know your shady things
That's why you feel like I'm an eyesore around you
I thought you were taking this opportunity to get rid of me
It turns out there is such a deep intention.
It’s amazing Bai Zhengtai
You bastard
Why? Do you think you are a good leader?
Let the juniors wash your underwear and deal with the mess for you
When you're done, just kick it away
In the end, he is still pretending. Is this called a good leader?
you bastard
The biggest bad luck in my life
It’s because you are my master
When you get fired one day, I will return the words exactly as you said.
"You're just pretending to be an executive."
You're really looking for death, bastard
- What?
- Bastard!
I've done so much for you, how could you do this?
I didn't do any work? Me?
- Hello!
- You bastard
Pretending to be at work?
- So are you working?
- How can you say that?
Just play damn golf all day long!
- Hey! I've done so much for you
- Damn it!
You, of all people, can't do this to me, asshole!
Why can't I? You bastard!
-"Asshole"?
- You might as well...
- What's going on?
- You are so...
I got into big trouble
But my heart feels inexplicably calm
The mind is also very clear
It's because
no matter what the result
Has the uncertainty finally disappeared?
Ha Jin, I'm sorry.
Looks like I'll stop here
They said it was delicious
hello
I need to put on more sunscreen
I brought it
- Hey
- hello
- Let's go!
- Let's go
- OK, let's go
- Let's go!
Let's all swing together
- Swing left!
- Swing right Swing up and down
- Swing
awesome
Are you in such a hurry? You can’t even wait for the weekend
- Hello, senior
- Just call and talk about this kind of thing.
Oops
It seems that you have suffered a lot
let's go in
OK
long time no see
This place has changed so much
Just make a phone call. Why go all the way?
And it’s the weekend
I don't want to come either
Minister Kim
Huh?
You should listen to what Executive Bai has to say.
I told him I'll tell you
But he insisted on doing it himself and arranged the meeting.
As a result, you two didn’t talk about anything serious.
Oops
What's the business?
ok
let me explain
ACT plans to lay off employees
Of course the employees at the headquarters will be laid off.
The Asan factory also needs to make adjustments.
So...
we need your help
- Me?
- Right
I'm just from the security management group
The human resources team here
Working with the production team
Don't listen to us at all
Someone I can turn to
You are the only one left, senior
What exactly do I need to do?
If security violation records are accumulated
We can use this as an excuse to force them to resign.
We have used this method before
Senior
Only 20 people are needed
Please make a list by next week
The headquarters assigns you a task
Be sure to finish it cleanly
As long as this thing can be done
No need for Executive Bai
I promise to transfer you back to the headquarters
You used to be quite tired of serving Bai Zhengtai, right?
Isn't it?
This time you treat me as a favor
Oh and...
This is for you
(ACT Voluntary Separation Scheme)
Don't get me wrong, there will be an announcement on Monday
Now for you. You can take a look first.
But even if you really misunderstood, I can't help it
Senior, I'm leaving first
take care
Please read that notice carefully
Hello
- Hello
good morning
Six and Seven Waist Exercises
One, two, three, four
five, six, seven, eight
Two, two, three, four, five, six, seven steps
One, two, three, four
five, six
Do a good job
three, four, five, six
seven, eight
One, two, three...
three, four, five, six, seven, eight
one, two
Do safety drills well
Two
five, six, seven, eight
One, two, three, four
two, two, three, four
five, six, seven
Please do safety exercises for me!
"Minister Kim's Dream Life"
Ladders without a working platform violate safety regulations
Clean up quickly! Hurry up!
I vaguely heard the wind
Said your team leader is coming back
Why does Minister Kim need to make the list?
(Voluntary resignation application)
You usually don’t even look at the factory.
Why did it suddenly change?
I'm working
(Violation of safety regulations)
Hand in that list
Can he be transferred back to the headquarters from the factory?
It would be nice to let you be an errand boy.
Otherwise, what else can you do?
You bastard
Let’s work hard. If you don’t want to work, just leave.
Hello, uncle
Think about how to stay in the company
Hold on as long as you can
This is the duty of being a parent
Come back to the headquarters and bring what you need to prepare.
Is this really “work”?
No matter what I think...
I don’t think this can be considered work.
Subtitle translation: Cheng Jiayue